

Profile

I am an emerging Software Developer currently enrolled at Nashville Software School in a Full-Stack Web Development Cohort. Upon completing the cohort in May 2023, I will be seeking a position as a Software Developer.

Prior to web development, I spent two years in public accounting in EY's assurance practice, where I helped perform audits for large public and private companies. While at EY, I received my CPA licensure in the state of Tennessee.

In addition to my professional career, I write a newsletter called MWF @ 8 about emerging technology, society & culture, and history. I also have a podcast series about interesting Biographies and Autobiographies called DyerNotes.

DAVIS DYER

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Education

BS - Business Administration, University of Tennessee University of Tennesse, Knoxville | 2015 - 2019

Master's of Accountancy, University of Tennessee University of Tennessee, Knoxville | 2019 - 2020

Experience

Software Developer

Nashville School of Software | 2022 - Present

I am currently enrolled in a Full-Stack Web Development cohort with NSS. The focus is on front-end capabilities in HTML, CSS, Javascript, and React, and back-end capabilities in Node.js and C#

Working daily with development teams in a virtual environment where we focus on problem-solving and effective communication

Building applications with different languages for agile project development

Assurance Services at EY

Ernst & Young (EY) | 2019 - 2022

Planned, coordinated, and conducted financial statement audit engagements for public and privately held companies with a focus on quality, operational excellence, and innovation.

Served clients across various industries, including: Fintech, Healthcare, Energy, Entertainment, Hospitality and Manufacturing, with annual revenues ranging from \$100M to \$2B.

Performed audit engagement services for a large private company acquisition.

Worked on diverse audit teams across the world to effectively perform audit procedures.

Tax Preparer

Tarwater & Co | 2019

Worked with a variety of clients on various tax reporting issues

Filed 1040, 1095, 1120, & K1s for clients of all sizes

Collaborated with accounting management on reporting questions to come to a compliant conclusion

Middle School Basketball Coach

Christian Academy of Knoxville 2016 - 2018

€oached JV and Varsity Middle School basketball teams while full-time in undergraduate business school.

Coordinated with parents on logistical details of the season (practice, games, tournaments, etc.)

Built practice schedules to motivate and encourage players to pull the best out of themselves each day

Content Creator

Newsletter

MWF @ 8

Technology | 2020-Present

Write a newsletter centered around emerging tech, history, and society & culture

Manage a subscriber base for whom I consistently publish content for

Gained invaluable writing skills that have helped me communicate more effectively

Podcast

DYERNOTES

History | 2022-Present

Publish a podcast focused on biographies and autobiographies

Developing verbal skills to communicate a variety of topics effectively

Combining informational and entertaining message delivery to my audience

C#

MySQL

Python

Node.js

PYTHON FOR DATA SCIENCE AND MACHINE

Skills

HTML

React

CSS

Front-End Developer

Back-End Development

Courses

2020

JavaScript

React Native

	LEARNING <i>Udemy</i>
2020	BLOCKCHAIN A-Z: HOW TO BUILD YOUR FIRST BLOCKCHAIN AND CRYPTOCURRENCY Udemy
2020	ETHEREUM BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER BOOTCAMP WITH SOLIDITY

in /davis-dyer-1

■ davis.dyer@icloud.com

Nashville, TN615-477-0458

Contact

\(\mathcal{O}\) /davis-dyer

2021 ETHEREUM DECENTRALIZED APPLICATION DESIGN AND DEVELOPMENT

Udemy

2021	THE ULTIMATE MYSQL BOOTCAMP Udemy
2021	THE COMPLETE PYTHON BOOTCAMP Udemy
2021	AWS SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT - ASSOCIATE Udemy